♪♪
[Hobbs]
You are here because
your brother
will join us tomorrow.
I know that you and my
predecessor had an arrangement,
but I am not Kareem.
This is my castle now.
Kyle shot me,
and I'm the fucking bad guy.
Tell them why you did it.
This is a house
of fucking cards, Trace,
and I can't be the reason
that it comes falling down.
Give me Sawyer.
I'll forget about
Charlie and Morrissey.
- I can't help you.
- That's a shame.
♪ dramatic music ♪
[train horn blows]
[Ian]
This fucking train
- decapitated these fuckers.
- [Mike] Jesus.
Well, this... this is
the devil we don't know.
[Raphael]
Bogotá's not budging.
Looks like we gonna have to
stand by that last installment.
- Bullshit.
- We don't, we squabble.
Mike. Somebody took a shot
at the big man.
[sirens wailing]
If anything happens
to my brother,
there's gonna be consequences.
[grunts, groans]
[Callahan]
You want to live,
do not go to sick bay.
You heal right here.
♪ pensive music ♪
I believe in Jesus Christ,
His only son, our Lord,
conceived by the Holy Ghost,
was crucified,
died and was buried.
He descended into Hell...
[continues indistinctly]
[Barnes]
Today is the day, today,
not fucking tomorrow.
No, no. It'll have to be.
They fucking lie!
They always lie!
[praying inmate]
...and life everlasting. Amen.
Our Father, who art in Heaven,
hallowed be Thy Name.
Thy kingdom come,
Thy will be done,
- on Earth as it is in heaven.
- ♪ slow, solemn music ♪
Give us this day
our daily bread.
- [groans]
- [praying inmate] Forgive those
- who trespass against us...
- [grunts]
[indistinct chatter]
[praying inmate]
Deliver us from evil...
[Kyle groaning softly]
Settling in is a bitch.
- [Kyle groans]
- Never easy.
[indistinct praying]
You alive, brother?
Knock once for "yes,"
twice for "no."
[Barnes]
Been over a week, goddamn it.
I got to see my counselor today!
T-O-D-A-Y, to-fucking-day!
[grunts]
Get me out of this cage!
I need to see my counselor!
I haven't seen my counselor
in a week, okay?! Goddamn it!
[grunts]
- ♪ slow, suspenseful music
- Shit.
[praying inmate]
...hallowed be Thy name.
Barnes, step away from the bars!
You're seeing your counselor
tomorrow, okay?
- Cut the bullshit. Be quiet.
- [Barnes] Get over here!
Hey, I don't know you.
Oh, God. Listen to me.
- I...
- They told you last night
that you're seeing your
counselor tomorrow, I promise.
Step away from the bars.
[Cindy]
Step away...
- You cunt.
- from the bars. Step... away...
- You cunt!
- Now!
I believe in the Holy Spirit,
the communion of saints
the forgiveness of sins,
the resurrection
of the body
and life everlasting.
- [grunts]
- Oh, my God!
[groaning]
[Kyle]
Officer?
Officer, call for backup.
- [panting]
- Stephens, I need help
in Ad Seg. I need immediate
backup. We got a prisoner down.
We got a prisoner down.
I need immediate backup.
[inmates clamoring]
[lock buzzes]
[Cindy]
Call 911!
[Cindy groans]
[Clyde]
Holy fuck.
[Breen]
Get the captain down here.
- [inmates clamoring]
- [exhales]
Fucking Mondays.
[Cindy groaning]
♪ slow, intriguing music ♪
♪
[engine revving]
I'm on my way to you. Getting in
before Hobbs gets there,
all right?
Make sure
there's no bullshit at the gate.
[tires squealing]
- All right. I'm on it.
- Carney, if you were on it,
none of this would be happening,
would it?
If you were on it,
my brother wouldn't be
a fucking punching bag.
If you were on it...
[inhales]
I'm doing what the fuck I can,
I promise you,
- I'll try.
- Are you eating right now?
Yeah, I'm fucking eating.
It's breakfast.
Jesus Christ, Carney.
This is not snack time.
I'll get you through the gate,
all right?
And I'll keep my eyes on Kyle,
that's... the best I can do.
This new warden
and her little deputy, Torres--
shit, they've-they've got
my balls in a vice.
I've got no sway.
Carney, I think it's time
maybe you put on a smile,
shake some hands,
make some new friends,
figure it the fuck out.
[engine revving]
What's that CO in Ad Seg?
The new one?
- The one you have a crush on?
- Cindy... Stephens. Why?
Russell's tonight.
After you clock out, be there.
I want to meet her.
Thank you. Bye.
- [line ringing]
- [sighs]
- Hi. This is Tracy. Please...
- Fuck. Goddamn it.
...leave a message.
and I'll get back to you
- as soon as possible.
- [beep]
Hey, Trace, it's me.
Look, before you go visit Kyle,
please call me first.
It's important.
- Thank you.
- [train signal bell clanging]
- Fuck!
[tires squealing]
- [train horn blowing]
- [bell clanging]
- [engine revving]
- [tires squealing]
[Ian]
Let's try this again.
- What's your fucking name?
- ¿Cómo se llama?
Abogado.
Who told you
to take out Bunny Washington?
- Abogado.
- [Ian] Okay, fuck it.
I'm gonna throw a big word down
here, fucker. "Reciprocity."
Know what that means?
Means you give me something,
I give you something back. Now,
you tell me who called the hit,
I get you a fucking lawyer,
you walk the fuck out of here.
Abogado.
Fucking Jesus Christ,
English, por favor.
- Abogado.
- "Abo..."
Nobody cares
about your avocados. All right?
Nobody gives a fuck.
I get what you're saying.
"I need a lawyer."
You got no ID, fucker.
You don't fucking exist.
So, here's what I'm thinking.
Maybe we put you
downstairs in a goddamn cell.
Huh?
¿Comprende, amigo?
And do yourself a fucking favor.
Give me something
in my native tongue.
I know you fucking speak it.
Hablo English.
Come on, Pablo.
Hablo English. Hablo.
[mocking]
Hablo English?
[high-pitched]
- ♪ slow, suspenseful music
- Fuck you.
I told you! You owe me
five bucks. Thank you, sir.
- Motherfucker.
- Thanks, big boss.
♪ tense, atmospheric music ♪
♪ She'll be driving
six white horses ♪
♪ Driving six
white horses ♪
♪ Driving six white horses
when she comes ♪
[vehicle door closes]
Heard you had
some static yesterday.
Distractions.
Bogotá go after the Russians,
come at me,
I'll pay 'em a visit soon.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
It wasn't the Colombians
took out Brighton Beach.
That you?
A gift to my enterprising
young brother.
Show you my intent.
What you expect in return?
Partnership, 'cause
I've been watching you, Deverin.
What you won's been hard-fought.
- You need an ally.
- I never did before.
Well, your move on Moscow opened
up some prime real estate.
The Russians held
that border pipeline
for years,
and now there's a vacuum.
And they'll come back and fill
it, or the Mexicans, the Aryans.
I mean, the cartel just tried
to take you out.
Now, I'd see
that you get to keep
what you've earned, Deverin.
Only family call me that, Frank.
Well, shit.
[both laughs]
A rabbit's something
to be chased, right?
A fearful creature.
Now, is that you, son?
Are you fearful?
Don't fear a goddamn thing.
Now, I'm thankful for the gift.
What do you want in return?
A future.
You coming up or not?
All right.
Yo, Jake,
we're doing this private.
["Time Out" by Count Basie
and His Orchestra playing]
♪
I'm an insulated man, D,
a legitimized man.
I outsource, I franchise,
I delegate.
I own this yard
we're sitting in right now,
and I use it to run product.
And what I offer you is
cross-border transport.
Security. For 30%.
♪
Ten sound better.
20, then. Split the difference.
All right. We gonna do this.
But with respect,
I know your rep,
but I ain't in the business of
taking anybody's word for shit.
I hear you.
I'm gonna meet every player,
every rider
on this here Pony Express.
I wouldn't have it
any other way.
You're gonna meet
everybody in the network.
See, I'm in the business
of paying shit forward, D.
For real.
But I have a request, too.
You misspoke before.
You have a partner.
It's time I met the mayor.
[chuckling]
- Mike.
- Hobbs.
Had I known you'd be here,
I would've
ordered for two
at the drive-thru.
So, you want to tell me
what the fuck happened?
I mean,
we just talked about this.
But not 24 hours later,
my brother gets beaten
to a pulp in your prison.
Want to explain that?
- Your brother--
- Kyle.
- McLusky. Yeah.
- Right.
I am sorry
that Kyle got into a fight.
Fight?
It's not a playground.
- No. No, it is not.
- Right? Right?
But you know the world, Mike,
you know this life.
- Mm-hmm.
- I am not in control
of every variable, and it is not
my job to reach out
to family every time
there's an incident.
Not what you sang yesterday.
You rule with an iron fist.
But a velvet glove.
I am still settling in, Mike.
Just give me a beat.
Yeah.
Well, if you can't hold up
your end of the bargain,
I can't hold up mine.
We have no bargain.
Oh, so you didn't promise
to look after my brother?
I told you
I would keep him alive. Is he?
I am a woman of my word.
♪ slow, ominous music ♪
Okay, from this point on...
[sighs]
...anything that happens
to my brother in your prison,
I'll make sure happens to you.
Okay?
I, too, am a man of my word.
Thank you. You okay?
Yeah.
I think
it's time to reassign Carney.
- So soon?
- Yeah.
Vestiges of the past.
Should've done it day one.
[engine revving]
Little man doesn't know
where his bread is buttered.
[groaning, wincing]
[groans] Fuck.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
[groaning loudly]
[Callahan]
Check your mailbox.
Front door, brother.
♪ slow, eerie music ♪
♪
[Kyle groaning softly]
[groans, pants]
[panting]
♪
[Callahan]
You need distraction.
Few puffs won't give you cancer.
[train bell clanging]
[siren wailing in distance]
Hey, tell me
Raphael's got a line
on that motherfucker
who put hands on my brother?
Some shitcake trying
to make his bones, is the word.
Yeah, any affiliation?
None to speak of.
Just a garden-variety
Ritz cracker,
straight from the big box,
you feel me?
If it's sanctioned,
you'd know it, right?
It's been months since them
Aryans could've made that play.
- And the Russians?
- Nah.
The Red Scare's over, baby.
Take the win.
[sighs] Well, Bogotá comes
at you on the streets,
Raphael feel that inside?
They flexing.
- Yeah.
- Greedy as anybody,
but they smart, too. Know when
to stand, know when to sit.
- Shit. Shit.
- And to play it up
when they want something.
But these little skirmishes
ain't no war, Mike.
- Not yet. Not yet.
- Nah.
Stealth mode, papi.
Colombians ain't gonna bother
your brother none, all right?
They sure as shit bothered
the Russians on the tracks.
Stealth mode, my ass.
Yeah. Sure enough, sure enough.
Sure enough.
Your poker face is for shit,
Bunny.
That's 'cause I got something
to share.
[laughing]
Yeah.
- [Bunny chuckles]
- You think?
Wasn't the cartel did Moscow.
♪ slow, ominous music ♪
Was it you, Bunny?
Frank Moses.
Oldhead out of Detroit.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah, yeah, I know him, yeah.
Russians was his gift to me.
There ain't no such thing
as gifts, Bunny.
Fucking give you plenty.
Quit fucking around.
What are you doing?
We joining forces.
I get cover from an OG
who ain't never done time.
He gets his dough,
I make way more,
you get peace in your valley.
Sounds like escalation to me.
Nah, no.
That man spent decades
diversifying his assets,
and now he finna cash out.
Spend the rest of his days
in Saint Croix. [laughing]
Yeah, who isn't, huh?
Life is short, man.
I'm doing it right now, man.
I'm enterprising.
Well, look, you knew the burden
that outsiders bring upon us.
We don't have to keep
taking out the trash, man.
I wouldn't
venture out with this shit
if I didn't see an opportunity.
Yeah?
And I ain't going in blind.
I see the hazard,
and you know I'll handle.
Well, it ain't you
I'm worried about.
♪ slow, eerie music ♪
I appreciate that.
Moses wants an audience.
Yeah.
I mean, that man coming correct.
- Okay.
- Coming with respect.
Just meet with him,
that's all I ask.
Yeah, I'll meet with him.
Raphael meets the man
put hands on my brother.
That motherfucker gonna hear
that shit loud and clear, Mike.
Loud and clear.
♪ slow, ominous music ♪
♪
[Clyde]
17, got a visit.
[lock buzzes]
Give me your hands.
Step back.
Step out.
[cell door rumbles shut]
Let's go.
♪ slow, eerie music ♪
♪
[Kyle winces]
Hey, Clyde, I got it from here.
Why don't you get back
to your fucking Sudoku,
crosswords, whatever.
I'll take him.
Ain't got to twist my arm,
Carnoscopy.
- [buzzer sounding]
- Stephens, hang back, I got him.
Jesus Christ, man,
I'm fucking sorry.
[groans]
It's not your fault.
Mike's working every angle,
I'm fucking--
I promise you,
this won't happen again.
[sighs] All right. I know.
[winces]
[buzzer sounds]
[gasps, groans]
Oh, fuck.
- Hold on. Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
- [groaning] Hey.
Look at me. Look at me. Hey.
- Breathe through your nose.
- [groaning]
Breathe through your nose.
Stand up slowly.
- [groans]
- Slowly stand.
- Stand. You got this.
- [groaning]
- Breathe, breathe. Like that.
Is this, uh...
is this Mike I'm seeing?
No, it's Tracy.
- [KYLE] Oh, fuck no.
- [buzzer sounds]
- No, no, no.
- No, no, no. Now, look at me--
She can't see me... [inhales]
- She can't see me like this.
- Kyle.
I don't want her
to see me like this.
Kyle, look, look, look, look.
I don't want her
to see me like this.
Hey, stop. Stop.
Just fucking stop. Okay?
- [groans] Fuck.
- You can't leave her
down there like that.
It'll make shit worse.
She'll just start imagining
what happened to you.
Come on. Come on, come on. Come
on, come on, come on. Come on.
Come on, brother.
[wincing, groaning]
[door closes]
- I'll buy you some time.
- Okay.
[Kyle sighs]
Kyle, what the fuck happened?
It's not as bad as it looks.
Guess I should see
the other guy.
Did they take you
to the infirmary?
I didn't need it, Trace.
I'm okay.
Not until a doc sees it,
you're-you're not.
We don't know if your ribs
are bruised or broken.
- If there's a fracture...
- Please. Please, please.
...there's a chance
that you're bleeding internally.
Hey, hey. I said I'm okay.
Does it hurt to breathe?
I can't go to the infirmary.
You know that.
Well, maybe I go see
the new warden and ask
what kind of shop
she's fucking running here.
I talked to Carney,
Mike's taking care of it, Trace.
Yeah.
Bang-up fucking job so far.
[sighs]
♪ slow, melancholy music ♪
Look...
if you can't handle coming here
and seeing me like this,
I get it.
Hey, there is nothing I can't--
You don't have to come here,
is what I'm saying.
There's nothing I can't handle.
I don't want
to go 12 rounds with you.
Tough shit.
Tough shit. Okay.
This is what you married, Kyle.
Can't turn it off.
[laughs]
I surrender. I surrender.
Goddamn right you surrender.
I'm not leaving you alone, okay?
Not a fucking chance.
I see what happens
when family stops coming.
The ones inside break.
So don't ask me to stop,
because you know I won't.
[sighs]
I won't.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
How's our little guy?
- [exhales]
- Huh?
Hey, come on. Come on.
[Tracy sniffles]
[Kyle chuckles]
Let's go, ladies, let's go.
On the ice.
Skates are tight.
Don't want to see any
ankle-burners out there.
Let's go!
[indistinct shouting]
Mike.
[Mike]
Fuck you doing here?
- You got community service?
- How's our boy?
Ah, he's beat to shit,
but Carney says he's all right.
What the fuck is Carney doing?
You got a line on the hitter?
It's being handled.
We know who hit Bunny?
The Colombian kid we took in
is not saying shit.
There's some weird fuckery
with that. Can you not raise
the fucking puck?
Hey. Watch your language.
- Friggin' puck. My bad.
- Fucking Jesus Christ.
I'm keeping 'em out of fucking
juvie, man. Jesus Christ.
- Is that what you're doing?
- [Stevie] Kid we got in the box,
not much older than these guys,
man. Ancient eyes, Mikey.
Yeah, how old we talking?
Like, 20. Maybe, at the most.
Kid has seen
some haunting shit, man.
I'm in there,
he just tells me to fuck off.
Yeah, well,
I might like the guy already.
- Most English we got out of him.
- [Ian] We could charge
this fucking kid if we knew
who the fuck we're charging.
- Mm.
- But the prints came back.
They went nowhere.
We got nothing.
Well, cut him loose.
♪ slow, suspenseful music ♪
[Ian]
To be clear,
cut loose
a fucking cartel soldier
who took a shot
at Bunny Washington,
then turned
on Kingstown's finest?
- Uh, namely me and Ian--
- Namely us.
Well, you said you have nothing.
Right?
He's unarmed. Cut him loose,
see where he goes.
Mikey, when he gets on
the next bus to fucking Bogotá?
Then what are we doing?
We don't know any more
than we know now, do we?
Colombians are flexing
on both sides of the walls.
Let's see
who's calling the shots.
- Yeah.
- Figure that out.
[water running]
♪ suspenseful, pulsing music ♪
♪
[grunting]
[groaning]
[garbled radio transmission]
♪ quiet, tense music ♪
[Ian]
Come on, you fucker.
Give me something good here.
♪ slow, mysterious music ♪
♪
This fucking kid's doomed.
Living in an abandoned shithole.
[Stevie]
What, doomed? You grow up
- in a mansion? Huh?
- [phone buzzing]
No shit. Hey, Captain.
[Walter] Need you back
at the station, Ferguson.
Yeah, we're right in the middle
of something here, Cap.
- Not a request.
- [Ian] It's kind of important.
- Stevie and I are on a stakeout.
- Keno's on his way.
I'm counting you down
right fucking now.
Shit. Captain's cursing.
He's trying to put
on a show for somebody.
- [car engine starts]
- Yeah.
[phone buzzing]
[Bunny]
It's done, Mike.
That message went out?
Broadcast large.
Baby bro gonna sleep good
tonight.
Thanks, Bunny.
[sniffles]
Shit.
- What'd I do now?
- You got a VIP out in chairs.
We don't have VIPs here.
He says
his name is Frank Moses.
- [Rebecca pouring coffee]
- He alone?
He is, 'cause his name alone
carries enough weight
and consequence.
Yeah, yeah, I know who he is,
Rebecca,
and I knew that he was gonna
come. Just didn't know when.
Now we do. Thank you.
Mike, what business do we have
with Detroit?
We don't. None.
Not my business, not yours.
'Cause you don't pay me enough
for Motor City.
What, you want a raise?
You can have a raise
fast as you can ask.
Is that what you want?
This isn't a joke.
That man's murderous.
Who isn't, in this fucking town?
Send him in, you'll never have
to see him again.
- Okay? I promise.
- [sighs]
What's the matter?
You just got a raise.
You're priceless.
Priceless, I say.
[door opens, closes]
Mr. Moses?
Thank you very kindly, miss.
Mr. Moses.
Mr. McLusky.
Some coffee, water?
They're both flammable.
[chuckles]
I'm good.
- [clears throat]
- So, what can I do for you?
- Got someone inside?
- Got plenty inside.
Inside, six feet under,
heaven above.
That's not the kind of outreach
I seek.
Well, that's the only kind
we got.
Well, whatever keeps your name
on the door
and the checks coming in.
It is impossible not to notice
that you have a real gift.
Yeah, what's that?
Taking care of your town.
Well, I look after my friends.
Indeed. I've been watching
Deverin from afar, some time.
Impressive how he's able
to hold his own.
- Bunny is a force of nature.
- [laughs]
He is that, he is that.
But true dominance takes time.
I see my own ambition
in our friend.
I see his future.
See yours, too.
Oh, wow.
Are you some sort of prophet?
"A prophet is not without
honor, except in his hometown,
amongst his family,
and in his own household."
That's Mark 6:4.
Yeah. I'm a little rusty
on my Sunday school.
It means
I'm not from Kingstown, Mike,
so, maybe, being an outsider,
I can prophesy some.
Hustle as long as I have,
shit comes in shorthand.
You learn when to buy, when to
sell, who postures, who proves.
And you, son,
oh, you've proved yourself.
I don't know
what I can do for you.
There's nothing
that I can offer
that you don't already have.
You're about to have
a fresh plague of outsiders
descend on your town.
It's already started.
And wouldn't you rather
it just me?
♪ slow, eerie music ♪
I know the arrangement
that you and Bunny have.
It seems a bit generous
on your part.
It's not. I make a profit, Bunny
shaves off some of the risk.
It's a partnership.
And if I can better educate
the brother, it's all upside.
So, you're always once removed?
Or twice. Or thrice.
[chuckles]
So when the shit rains down,
your partners, they get wet,
you don't.
[laughing]
My partners profit.
And they know the risk.
Sorry.
I don't think I can provide
the outreach that you need.
This humble-pie act
don't suit you.
Deverin's won because of you,
the checks and balances
you maintain,
your control of the law.
I have friends
on both sides of the wall.
And I want your friends
to be mine, Mike.
So name your price.
Yeah, look,
I appreciate the offer,
and I know Bunny does, too,
but my payout is peace.
Or at least the promise of it,
you know?
Uh, not for profit.
Then I ask your blessing
while I shut things down.
You may see some death spasms,
but I promise you this:
Any loose ends, Deverin and I
will tie off with restraint.
Was that restraint
on the tracks?
[laughs]
I just finished
what you started, Mike,
with Sunter and Noskov.
You pitched
a solid eight innings,
I came in the ninth
and closed.
Almost like
we're partners already.
Appreciate this.
I'll be seeing you.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[indistinct chatter]
[knocks]
[Walter]
Shut the door.
- Have a seat.
- No, no, I'm good. I'll stand.
What'd you got?
Run the tape.
♪ slow, suspenseful music ♪
♪
Okay, and?
[Evelyn]
It's what I told you.
Ian, it's what I warned.
That last one?
That's you returning Charlie
to Anchor Bay
11 minutes after you left
Morrissey's house.
I can't leave a place
I've never been.
Evelyn, I mean, come on.
All right? You can run
that tape over and over again
all day every day,
because you know
what you're not gonna see
is me behind the wheel,
'cause I wasn't fucking there.
I mean-- the Captain--
Jesus Christ--
There's no license plate,
there's no fucking ID,
and you know
you don't have shit, right?
That's why you're here
fucking fishing. Come on.
Okay, look, out of respect
for this department--
That is a crock of shit. You
don't have any fucking respect.
I'm here as a courtesy, Ian,
to both of you.
Okay? 'Cause I am going
to the grand jury, and I am
going to press charges.
It is just a matter of time.
There's no fucking evidence.
That's just subjective
horseshit, Evelyn.
You see anything you want--
Loch Ness Monster, fat Elvis.
- You can't see a license plate.
- That is your car.
You know how many fucking
Dodge Chargers
are registered in the state
of Michigan? Look it up.
Fucking evidence.
That's not it.
Ian, I don't want to be here
any more than you do,
but I can't not do my job.
You know what you need to do.
- Your, uh...
- Keep it.
It'll give you time to process.
Consider the implications.
Oh, we'll get right back to you,
Counselor.
I mean, you can
keep your threats.
You don't have shit,
you never had shit,
you still don't have shit.
If you did, you'd bring it.
Have a nice day!
I mean, Jesus Christ,
you walked me
into that fucking buzzsaw?
Are you a cop
or a fucking doorman?
- But you were out of line, Ian.
- Out of line?
That's what you got for me?
Holy fuck.
Super fucking helpful, Captain.
♪
[indistinct chatter]
[garbled radio transmission]
The CI team sees this
as retaliation.
History of violence
finally caught up with him.
Of course it's retaliation.
His history of violence
includes the assault
on Kyle McLusky.
Big brother showing his reach.
- [whistles softly]
- I'm sorry, Nina.
This is on me. I should've been
way ahead of this.
No, no, this is on me.
This is the one priority now.
McLusky pulls no fucking strings
in my prison.
Understood. I'll make it so.
- Yes, I know you will, I know.
- [sighs]
We've dealt with worse, right?
Have we? I don't know.
God, this place.
[garbled radio transmission]
[indistinct chatter]
[sighs]
[Mike]
Hey.
How you doing? Here, got it?
- Yeah.
- You okay?
[sniffles]
You know I'm not.
Yeah, look,
I tried to warn you, Trace.
Wouldn't have made a difference.
Constant state of warning
in this family.
Yeah.
[Tracy sighs]
Well, it's a... all-around
fucked-up situation, you know?
But Kyle's making the best
of it, right?
Right. [sighs]
- Can you?
- This is
me making the best of it.
It's not his fault.
I know it's not his fault, Mike.
None of this is.
[sighs]
And Kyle's doing the right
thing, and he believes that.
And while he's in there,
he needs you to believe it, too.
I don't. I think it's bullshit.
[sniffles]
Trace, well, then,
can you just fake it?
[sighs]
I bring Mitch home
to an empty house, Mike,
every night.
I wake up every morning
without Kyle,
wake up when I've actually
slept, which is rare,
worried
that what happened to him
is-is happening
every fucking day.
- I'm faking it the best I can.
- Yeah.
Hey, look, um...
I'm sorry. I really am.
- Okay?
- [Baby Mitch fussing]
I know you are, and I know
you'd fix it if you could.
- [Baby Mitch crying]
- ♪ slow, dramatic music ♪
The only way Kyle gets
through this, and he sees
the other side of this thing
is if you got his back.
Without a doubt, without
a question, he's got to know it.
- [Baby Mitch cries loudly]
- [Mike] All right.
- I got to go, Mike. He's hungry.
- Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah. Let me know
if you need anything.
Thanks.
[Baby Mitch crying]
♪ slow, melancholy music ♪
[indistinct chatter]
♪ slow, suspenseful music ♪
♪
[speaking Spanish]
Hey! Hey, motherfucker!
- Back the fuck up!
- [grunts]
- What the fuck you doing?
- I ain't doing shit! [grunts]
Oh, yeah? Looks like you were
trying to go into the hole,
motherfucker. Get the fuck out
of here, you pinhead, before
I crack your skull open.
How far does your head have
to be up your own ass, Torres?
- Are you fucking braindead?
- It's under control, Doug.
Three paces.
You're lucky to be alive.
Some bush-league shit.
[siren wailing in distance]
[horn honks]
[Evelyn]
Okay, Karla, just
make it clear that nothing
comes out of his pocket, okay?
If the per diem doesn't cover
his daily wage,
I'll just write him
a check myself. Whatever.
[dings]
♪ pulsing, dramatic music ♪
[siren wailing]
♪
♪ eerie, slow music ♪
Oh. Shit.
You good, Big Man?
I'm too big
for this subcompact bullshit.
[knocking]
Trouble you for a word, ma'am?
You just caught me, Carney.
What's up?
It's been a day.
Let's not keep
your loved ones waiting.
Yeah, I won't keep you long.
You got family, Warden?
Uh, yes, Carney, what is it?
I saw something earlier.
Something I can't really shake.
Oh?
Torres was tangled up
in some Spanish shit
with an inmate at chow.
Which inmate?
Roberto Cruz. Colombian hitter.
Nothing but bad news
as long as I've been here.
I hear you. Go on.
Warden, excuse me
for saying this.
I-I don't know
what country club you came from,
but you both need to know,
the convicts we keep here,
these guys are fucking killers.
They are the worst of the worst.
You need to keep your distance.
Seriously.
And Cruz?
That asshole?
A 50-fucking-foot pole,
pardon my French.
Pardoned and no offense taken.
Your experiences bring insights,
Carney. It's appreciated.
Keep it coming.
I will have a chat with Torres.
But know that we are prepared
to handle our wards,
any means necessary.
Have a good night.
- ♪ tense, dramatic music
- [briefcase clicks shut]
[engine revving]
[line ringing]
[clicks]
This partnership goes sideways,
I need to know.
Moses cuts bait, I need to know.
[scoffs] Well, fucking "hello"
to you, too, Mike.
And-- listen to me--
if you're gonna drop a body,
can you please do it out of town
and not make my life
more difficult
than it already is? Thank you.
Oh, I take it
you met the man, then?
Yeah, I did.
And?
And it's day by day, Bunny.
You know, you see a mentor,
I see a machine gun nest.
[laughing] He a way out is
what the fuck he is.
I don't take on no fresh risk
without no payday,
not for this shit.
Don't need muscle
to put up a fight against
them twitch-ass Colombians, neither.
No, this, Mike, this shit
right here, this alliance?
It's all about family,
I'm doing for mine.
Yeah, I hear you.
I understand.
Same as you do for yours, Mike.
We both owe something.
Bunny, I'm not saying
that Moses is
the wrong way to go here,
but if you're waiting
to take over his kingdom,
I wouldn't hold my breath.
[scoffs]
You know me better than that.
Oldhead don't push it forward,
and it comes to my blood?
I'm taking his fucking kingdom.
Protect what's ours.
That's what matters.
It's all that matters.
♪ tense, dramatic music ♪
- [overlapping chatter]
- [music playing]
[loud, overlapping chatter]
[music plays loudly]
- [overlapping chatter]
-***
[engine revving]
- Put somebody out front, too.
- [Lamar] I got you.
Chris.
Oh, hey, how you doing?
Good seeing you, man.
Good to see you. Yeah.
How y'all doing?
Where your mom at now?
Hey, baby, how you doing?
Hey, good to see you,
good to see you.
[chatter, laughter]
- How you doing, sir?
- What up?
- Hey.
- How y'all doing?
[overlapping chatter]
Kevin's in the back room.
All right.
[music playing
indistinctly under chatter]
♪ slow, eerie music ♪
The fuck you doing
up in here, nigga?
Bunny, I'm sorry. I'm--
What happened
to a fucking phone call?
[woman laughs]
I-I don't mean no disrespect.
I... I just needed a word,
just face-to-face.
- No, I'm good.
- No, you're not.
You're at my sister's birthday.
You gonna act like
you at a party,
and you're gonna fucking drink.
And speak.
Okay.
So, I was... I was thinking.
- Uh-huh.
- Maybe it's time
I move on from the Anchor.
Something I need to know?
This new warden.
Ain't-ain't much I can do.
Changing of the guards,
you know?
Just thinking maybe there's more
I could do outside,
bigger things.
See, that's your problem
right there.
You don't do the thinking.
I think.
As long as you do what's asked,
this motor gonna hum.
Now, nothing gonna last forever,
but it is what it is right now.
Yes, sir.
All you got to do
is play the game, all right?
You work the new warden
like you did the old.
You charm the fuck out of her,
man. Come on, man.
And you come near
my family again,
I'm gonna put a bullet
in your ass, nigga.
[laughter, chatter]
[Whitney]
I know damn well you ain't
doing business in my party.
Bounce.
Just giving a little free advice
to the young buck right there.
Yeah. Yeah, that reasons.
Don't see nobody paying
good money for your advice.
[scoffs]
God, you gonna go there?
- Oh, I've been there.
- Come on, sis.
I know some shit.
I've-I've seen some shit.
[scoffs] Mm-hmm. Spend even
one day in my life, I dare you.
Try being 40
with two kids, okay?
- [laughs]
- You've seen a lot.
Get your ass out of here!
[chuckling]
Happy birthday, Whitney.
- [laughing] Happy birthday.
- [chuckling]
[lights buzzing]
[Callahan]
Care package, brother.
Take it for the pain,
if you want, if it helps.
No rule says
infirmary can't come to us.
[Kyle grunting softly]
[wheezes]
[groans]
[panting]
[grunts]
[Callahan]
Some people aren't raised right.
Never taught to love
thy neighbor as thyself.
Just want to tell you,
sick fuck that gave you
that warm welcome?
Met his maker.
You got reach, brother.
Never knew a con kill for a cop.
That's the mother of anomalies.
Want to hear that story.
When you're ready, I'm all ears.
[sighs]
♪ slow, ominous music ♪
[rock music playing]
You Cindy?
I was starting to worry
I got stood up.
Nope.
Thanks. Uh, look,
could I get a whiskey, neat?
Great minds.
Yeah.
[clears throat]
Fuck's Carney?
He said he's gonna be here
in ten minutes...
30 minutes ago.
Yeah, right. If a ball needs
to be dropped...
- Listen, I...
- Thank you.
I can't really w-wait around.
That right?
What else you got going on?
I got three kids
to put to bed, so,
why don't you just tell me
what it is you need?
I'm assuming
it's not Carney contingent.
- Yeah. No, it's not.
- Hmm.
It's about your brother?
Yeah, Kyle.
He was just processed.
And he's not to be fucked with?
- And he was.
- Yeah.
♪
Look, I'm really sorry.
I'm keeping an eye on him,
and he is healing.
Look, uh, my brother is doing
time for a very good reason.
He's not a criminal.
He's a family man,
and he's not suited
for life inside.
So, here's where you come in.
I need a friendly face
for him, inside.
I need your eyes and ears
on him for me.
When he wakes up, to the yard,
to the showers, till lights out.
[Mike clears throat]
Yeah, okay.
I'll also need you
to pick up when I call.
You'd be my lifeline.
I'm... a few days
out of training.
- That's good.
- I could not be more green.
[sighs]
All right, look,
as long
as I'm not pissing anybody off,
or crossing any DOC red lines,
I will pick up your phone calls.
I'll give him a nod
from time to time. All right?
You know, there is a lot
of inmate turnover in Ad Seg.
Guys in there 'cause
they cause a lot of trouble,
others 'cause
they want to avoid it.
Yeah, it seems so.
I need to know who the fuck
is in there with Kyle.
I need that list.
In case someone means him harm?
Goddamn right.
♪
[microwave beeping]
[indistinct voices on TV]
Hey.
Pop, it's coming.
Just give me a second.
[TV chatter continues]
[Carney sniffles]
[sniffles]
...backhand,
and listen over the...
Always the highlights,
never the game.
- I never get that.
- [laughs]
Attention span.
What do you think?
They got a shot this year, Pop?
I'm gonna stay alive until I...
till I see the Stanley Cup
raised. [chuckles]
I don't want you
staying alive that long.
[laughs]
You can handle a fork and knife?
I look like an invalid,
smart ass?
Yeah. Careful. It's hot.
Listen, I'm gonna run out
for a little bit, okay?
Uh-huh.
- Don't die on me, you old fart.
- [chuckles]
[sniffles, sighs]
[TV playing indistinctly]
[sighs]
[two gunshots]
[TV continues playing
indistinctly]
[wind whistling]
[TV playing indistinctly]
[train whistle blowing]
- [TV plays quietly]
- [dogs barking]
[announcer]
Anthony added another lead
and closes it out, 4-2.